Lucas DAVID

31/12/1999

MASTER'S 2 BIOINFORMATICS STUDENT

PERSONAL DETAILS



(+33)6 45 23 06 35



lucasdavid85@hotmail.fr



2 rue du faubourg saint jean, Orleans, France



https://www.linkedin.com/in/lucas--david/

PROFILE

Graduate in biology and chemestry bachelor's degree, and after studying bioinformatics for the master's degree, I have discovered bioinformatics tools to accelerate the research. By my volunteering, I have acquired competences in project and people leading through an event preparation.

SKILLS

Computer skills



Tools and software









Native Intermediate

- Marathon, Running, triathlon M
- Music (Piano, Sing)

HOBBIES

• Travel: Italy, USA



EDUCATION

Bioinformatician

Nantes University (2017-2023)

Master in Bioinformatics (2021-2023) - ongoing

- Structural Bioinformatics, Project Management
 Bachelor 3 in Biological Chemistry (2020-2021)
- Chemestry component synthesis (practical work)

Bachelor in Biology and animal physiology (2017-2020)

Animal testing, homeostasis, cellular biology

INTERNSHIP

Intern in master 2 - ongoing

ICOA, Orléans - 6 month

• Amino acid reconstruction, molecular dynamics, python, Modeller

Internship in master 1

US2B, Nantes 4 month

- Structural Bioinformatics, docking
- Deep learning, Django, web developpment

WORK EXPERIENCE

Production operator

Nutréa, France 2 month

Factory worker

Maitre coq, France 5 month

IMPLICATION

Student Association's Treasurer

SciNaPSE, (2021-2022)

Association's teacher, team managing, project coordination

Student elected in Nantes University council

CFVU, (2019-2021)

Singer, pianist, musical coordinator musical theater

Imajine, (2015-2017)

illusical tileatei

REFERENCES

Stéphane Télétchéa, internship supervisor

US2B, Nantes university (+33)251125635 (France) stephane.teletche@univ-nantes.fr

Christine Sinoquet Head of the Master's program LS2N, Nantes University (+33)251125805

christine.sinoquet@ls2n.fr